<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Userli Documentation</title>
    <link>/userli/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Userli Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/userli/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>/userli/development/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/userli/development/documentation/</guid>
      <description>This page describes how to edit the documentation you&amp;rsquo;re currently reading. The whole documentation is located in the directory hugo. Change into this directory. All following commands are supposed to be run from here.
cd hugo  Requirements Download Hugo binary for your OS (Windows, Linux, Mac).
Editing Change files in hugo/content to edit the documentation. See the DocDock documentation for more information on how to organize content. Afterwards, commit your work to your repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/userli/development/code_of_conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/userli/development/code_of_conduct/</guid>
      <description>Our Pledge In the interest of fostering an open and welcoming environment, we as contributors and maintainers pledge to making participation in our project and our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
Our Standards Examples of behavior that contributes to creating a positive environment include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating release tarballs</title>
      <link>/userli/development/release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/userli/development/release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Release tarballs are the preferred way to install Userli. This page explains how to create them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding style</title>
      <link>/userli/development/coding_style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/userli/development/coding_style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We use the default Symfony coding style.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tests</title>
      <link>/userli/development/tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/userli/development/tests/</guid>
      <description> Linting, unit tests and functional tests cd vagrant &amp;amp;&amp;amp; vagrant up &amp;amp;&amp;amp; vagrant ssh make test make integration  Test checkpassword script cd vagrant &amp;amp;&amp;amp; vagrant up &amp;amp;&amp;amp; vagrant ssh bin/console doctrine:schema:create -n &amp;amp;&amp;amp; bin/console doctrine:fixture:load -n &amp;amp;&amp;amp; exit cd .. &amp;amp;&amp;amp; tests/test_checkpassword_login.sh  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>